dadaviz.com 2015-12-10

# None

This Privacy Policy explains how Dadaviz collects and uses data. If not otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms have the meaning given to them in the Dadaviz Terms of Use, which is available at dadaviz.com/pages/terms (the “Terms”). 

Dadaviz respects your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains Dadaviz’s policies regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of any information we receive. 

###  Information we Collect 

In order to use our Site and Services, you will be required to register and provide us with certain Personal Information. We also collect Personal Information when you make use of the Site and Services. “Personal Information” means information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a name or email address, or information about activities directly linked to a person, such as that person’s location. It is your voluntary decision whether to provide us with any such Personal Information, but if you refuse to provide such information we may not be able to register you to use the Site and the Services. 

If you use the Site or the Services by logging in through “Facebook Connect” or another social network, we may also receive personal information about you which is provided by such social network. Please check the policies of such social network in order to understand what information we receive. 

We collect such User Content that you provide to us. 

In addition, when you use Dadaviz certain information may be automatically gathered about your computer, browser, operating system, geo-location, IP address or mobile device, or in respect of any other of your activities using the Site or Services. 

###  How we Protect Information 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We will delete any information provided to us by a User upon the receipt of a written request by such User. We cannot restore information that we have deleted. 

###  How we Use Information 

Except as expressly set forth herein, we will not share your Personal Information with third parties without your explicit permission, except when required by law, regulation, subpoena or court order or in order to cooperate with an investigation by a law enforcement body. We may use Personal Information internally – for example, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to make Dadaviz more useful, or to customize Dadaviz and personalize its content for you. 

We display such User Content that you upload on the Site and/or Services. 

In addition, by analyzing all information we receive, including all information concerning Users, we may compile statistical information across a variety of platforms and Users (“Statistical Information”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new products and services can be considered and so existing products and services can be tailored to customer desires. Statistical Information is anonymous and we will not link Statistical Information to any Personal Information. We may share such Statistical Information with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion. We may provide non-Personal Information that we receive to Google Analytics in order to receive an analysis of the use of our Site and Services. 

###  Feedback 

When you give feedback of Contributors through Dadaviz or through other social media platforms, please remember that any information disclosed in this venue may be automatically made public, and such information will not be considered Personal Information by Dadaviz. You should exercise caution when disclosing any information (including Personal Information) in such a venue, as you do not know who will access or use such information and for what purposes. 

###  Cookies 

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a visitor's browser. The browser provides this piece of text to the device of the originating visitor when this visitor returns. Dadaviz uses cookies to help personalize your Dadaviz experience. A “persistent” cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations across Site visits. Also, if you log in to Dadaviz, such a cookie will be used to recognize you as a valid user so you will not need to log in each time you use Dadaviz. Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change this setting so your browser either refuses all cookies or informs you when a cookie is being sent. Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that some features of Dadaviz may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed. 

###  Online Links to Other Sites 

Dadaviz Users can link to websites of third-parties that provide useful information/services. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to this third party and is subject to that third-party’s provider’s privacy policy. Except as described above, Dadaviz is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of websites to which we link. Links from our Site or Services to third-parties or other websites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of each website before providing them with personal information. We cannot be held responsible for any third-party websites and accessing their content will be subject to their own privacy policies, which again - we advise you to check. 

###  Use of Dadaviz by Children 

Dadaviz does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 14. In the event you become aware that an individual under the age of 14 has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately. 

Correcting or Updating your Information. We allow you to view the information you provided during registration and to alter any data, inaccuracies or errors. To request such access, or correct, update, or amend your personal information please contact us at the following email address: [info@dadaviz.com](mailto:info@dadaviz.com). We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at the email address listed above. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

###  Communications 

We may send you email or other messages about us or our products and services. By accepting the Terms of Service for the Services (including the terms of this Privacy Policy which are incorporated therein) or using the Site or Services, you affirmatively consent to receive such commercial messages. As a registered member, you can remove your personal information from our mailing list and stop receiving future communication from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at [info@dadaviz.com](mailto:info@dadaviz.com). You will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages in any such email or other message we send. Please note that we reserve the right to send you service related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions on this Site and/or Services, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you cancel your account. 

###  Other Uses or Transfer of Your Information 

We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity, behavior or digital content of any User suspected to have engaged in illegal or infringing behavior. In providing the Services, we may use subcontractors that are located in countries other than your own, and send them information we receive. For example, we may send your information to any countries outside the United States or the European Economic Area. All our subcontractors will be subject to non-disclosure and non-use obligations. Nevertheless, some countries may have levels of protection of personal and other information which are not as high as in your country of residence or business. We may transfer our databases containing your Personal Information if we sell our business or part of it. 

###  Changes 

Dadaviz may update this Privacy Policy from time to time - we encourage you to review it periodically. 

###  Comments and Questions 

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@dadaviz.com](mailto:info@dadaviz.com)

_Last updated: September 2014_
